What do you think of when I say the word "design"?
[AI] 当我说“设计”这个词时，你会怎么想？
You probably think of things like this.
[AI] 你可能会想到这样的事情。
finely crafted objects that you can hold in your hand.
[AI] 精心制作的物品，你可以拿在手里。
or maybe logos and posters and maps
[AI] 或者是商标、海报和地图
that visually explain things.
[AI] 可以直观地解释事情。
classic icons of timeless design.
[AI] 永恒设计的经典图标。
But I'm not here to talk about that kind of design.
[AI] 但我不是来这里谈论这种设计的。
I want to talk about the kind
[AI] 我想谈谈那种
that you probably use every day
[AI] 你可能每天都在用
and may not give much thought to.
[AI] 而且可能不会考虑太多。
designs that change all the time
[AI] 不断变化的设计
and that live inside your pocket.
[AI] 那就住在你的口袋里。
I'm talking about the design
[AI] 我说的是设计
of digital experiences
[AI] 数字体验
and specifically the design of systems
[AI] 特别是系统的设计
that are so big that their scale
[AI] 他们的规模如此之大
can be hard to comprehend.
[AI] 可能很难理解。
Consider the fact that Google processes
[AI] 考虑谷歌过程的事实
over one billion search queries every day.
[AI] 每天超过10亿次搜索查询。
that every minute. over 100 hours
[AI] 每分钟都是这样。超过100小时
of footage are uploaded to YouTube.
[AI] 视频被上传到YouTube。
That's more in a single day
[AI] 一天之内就有更多
than all three major U.S. networks broadcast
[AI] 比美国三大电视网广播的都多
in the last five years combined.
[AI] 在过去的五年里。
And Facebook transmitting the photos.
[AI] Facebook也在传送照片。
messages and stories
[AI] 信息和故事
of over 1.23 billion people.
[AI] 超过12.3亿人。
That's almost half of the Internet population.
[AI] 这几乎占互联网人口的一半。
and a sixth of humanity.
[AI] 人类的六分之一。
These are some of the products
[AI] 这些是一些产品
that I've helped design over the course of my career.
[AI] 在我的职业生涯中，我一直在帮助设计。
and their scale is so massive
[AI] 他们的规模是如此巨大
that they've produced unprecedented
[AI] 他们创造了前所未有的
design challenges.
[AI] 设计挑战。
But what is really hard
[AI] 但真正困难的是什么
about designing at scale is this:
[AI] 关于按比例设计，如下所示：
It's hard in part because
[AI] 这很难，部分原因是
it requires a combination of two things.
[AI] 它需要两件事的结合。
audacity and humility —
[AI] 厚颜无耻-
audacity to believe that the thing that you're making
[AI] 大胆地相信你正在做的事情
is something that the entire world wants and needs.
[AI] 是全世界都想要和需要的东西。
and humility to understand that as a designer.
[AI] 作为一名设计师，谦逊地理解这一点。
it's not about you or your portfolio.
[AI] 这与你或你的投资组合无关。
it's about the people that you're designing for.
[AI] 这是关于你为之设计的人。
and how your work just might help them
[AI] 你的工作对他们有什么帮助
live better lives.
[AI] 过更好的生活。
Now. unfortunately. there's no school
[AI] 现在不幸地没有学校
that offers the course Designing for Humanity 101.
[AI] 这提供了人性设计101课程。
I and the other designers
[AI] 我和其他设计师
who work on these kinds of products
[AI] 谁在做这类产品
have had to invent it as we go along.
[AI] 我们不得不在前进的过程中发明它。
and we are teaching ourselves
[AI] 我们在自学
the emerging best practices of designing at scale.
[AI] 大规模设计的新兴最佳实践。
and today I'd like share some of the things
[AI] 今天我想和大家分享一些事情
that we've learned over the years.
[AI] 这是我们多年来学到的。
Now. the first thing that you need to know
[AI] 现在你需要知道的第一件事
about designing at scale
[AI] 关于规模化设计
is that the little things really matter.
[AI] 小事情真的很重要。
Here's a really good example of how
[AI] 这里有一个很好的例子说明
a very tiny design element can make a big impact.
[AI] 一个非常微小的设计元素可以产生巨大的影响。
The team at Facebook that manages the Facebook "Like" button
[AI] 管理Facebook“喜欢”按钮的Facebook团队
decided that it needed to be redesigned.
[AI] 决定需要重新设计。
The button had kind of gotten out of sync with the evolution of our brand
[AI] 这个按钮与我们品牌的发展有点不同步
and it needed to be modernized.
[AI] 它需要现代化。
Now you might think. well. it's a tiny little button.
[AI] 现在你可能会想。好这是一个小小的按钮。
it probably is a pretty straightforward.
[AI] 这可能是一个非常简单的问题。
easy design assignment. but it wasn't.
[AI] 简单的设计任务。但事实并非如此。
Turns out. there were all kinds of constraints
[AI] 结果是。有各种各样的限制
for the design of this button.
[AI] 用于此按钮的设计。
You had to work within specific height and width parameters.
[AI] 您必须在特定的高度和宽度参数内工作。
You had to be careful to make it work
[AI] 你必须小心才能让它工作
in a bunch of different languages.
[AI] 用一大堆不同的语言。
and be careful about using fancy gradients or borders
[AI] 要小心使用奇特的渐变或边框
because it has to degrade gracefully
[AI] 因为它必须优雅地退化
in old web browsers.
[AI] 在旧的web浏览器中。
The truth is. designing this tiny little button
[AI] 事实是。设计这个小按钮
was a huge pain in the butt.
[AI] 屁股痛得厉害。
Now. this is the new version of the button.
[AI] 现在这是按钮的新版本。
and the designer who led this project estimates
[AI] 领导这个项目的设计师估计
that he spent over 280 hours
[AI] 他花了280多个小时
redesigning this button over the course of months.
[AI] 在几个月内重新设计此按钮。
Now. why would we spend so much time
[AI] 现在我们为什么要花这么多时间
on something so small?
[AI] 这么小的东西？
It's because when you're designing at scale.
[AI] 这是因为当你按比例设计时。
there's no such thing as a small detail.
[AI] 没有一个小细节。
This innocent little button
[AI] 这个天真的小按钮
is seen on average 22 billion times a day
[AI] 平均每天看220亿次
and on over 7.5 million websites.
[AI] 超过750万个网站。
It's one of the single most viewed design elements ever created.
[AI] 这是有史以来最受欢迎的设计元素之一。
Now that's a lot of pressure for a little button
[AI] 现在一个小按钮的压力很大
and the designer behind it.
[AI] 以及背后的设计师。
but with these kinds of products.
[AI] 但是有了这些产品。
you need to get even the tiny things right.
[AI] 你甚至需要把小事情做好。
Now. the next thing that you need to understand
[AI] 现在接下来你需要了解的是
is how to design with data.
[AI] 就是如何用数据进行设计。
Now. when you're working on products like this.
[AI] 现在当你在做这样的产品时。
you have incredible amounts of information
[AI] 你有大量的信息
about how people are using your product
[AI] 关于人们如何使用你的产品
that you can then use to influence
[AI] 你可以用它来影响别人
your design decisions.
[AI] 您的设计决策。
but it's not just as simple as following the numbers.
[AI] 但这不仅仅是简单的数字。
Let me give you an example
[AI] 让我给你举个例子
so that you can understand what I mean.
[AI] 这样你才能理解我的意思。
Facebook has had a tool for a long time
[AI] Facebook已经有了一个工具很长时间了
that allowed people to report photos
[AI] 这使得人们可以报告照片
that may be in violation of our community standards.
[AI] 这可能违反了我们的社区标准。
things like spam and abuse.
[AI] 像垃圾邮件和虐待之类的事情。
And there were a ton of photos reported.
[AI] 有大量的照片被报道。
but as it turns out.
[AI] 但事实证明。
only a small percentage were actually
[AI] 实际上只有一小部分人被解雇了
in violation of those community standards.
[AI] 违反了这些社区标准。
Most of them were just your typical party photo.
[AI] 大多数只是你典型的派对照片。
Now. to give you a specific hypothetical example.
[AI] 现在给你一个具体的假设例子。
let's say my friend Laura hypothetically
[AI] 假设我的朋友劳拉
uploads a picture of me
[AI] 上传我的照片
from a drunken night of karaoke.
[AI] 从一个醉醺醺的卡拉OK之夜。
This is purely hypothetical. I can assure you.
[AI] 这纯粹是假设。我可以向你保证。
(Laughter)
[AI] （众笑）
Now. incidentally.
[AI] 现在顺便提一句
you know how some people are kind of worried
[AI] 你知道有些人有多担心吗
that their boss or employee
[AI] 他们的老板或雇员
is going to discover embarrassing photos of them
[AI] 将会发现他们令人尴尬的照片
on Facebook?
[AI] 在Facebook上？
Do you know how hard that is to avoid
[AI] 你知道这有多难避免吗
when you actually work at Facebook?
[AI] 当你在Facebook工作的时候？
So anyway. there are lots of these photos
[AI] 所以无论如何。有很多这样的照片
being erroneously reported as spam and abuse.
[AI] 被错误地报告为垃圾邮件和滥用。
and one of the engineers on the team had a hunch.
[AI] 团队中的一名工程师有预感。
He really thought there was something else going on
[AI] 他真的以为还有别的事
and he was right.
[AI] 他是对的。
because when he looked through a bunch of the cases.
[AI] 因为当他看了一大堆案子的时候。
he found that most of them
[AI] 他发现他们中的大多数人
were from people who were requesting
[AI] 是从那些要求
the takedown of a photo of themselves.
[AI] 拍摄他们自己的照片。
Now this was a scenario that the team
[AI] 现在，这是一个团队
never even took into account before.
[AI] 以前从未考虑过。
So they added a new feature
[AI] 所以他们增加了一个新功能
that allowed people to message their friend
[AI] 这使得人们可以给他们的朋友发信息
to ask them to take the photo down.
[AI] 让他们把照片拍下来。
But it didn't work.
[AI] 但它不起作用。
Only 20 percent of people
[AI] 只有20%的人
sent the message to their friend.
[AI] 把消息发给他们的朋友。
So the team went back at it.
[AI] 于是球队又重新开始了。
They consulted with experts in conflict resolution.
[AI] 他们与解决冲突的专家进行了磋商。
They even studied the universal principles
[AI] 他们甚至研究了宇宙法则
of polite language.
[AI] 礼貌用语。
which I didn't even actually know existed
[AI] 我甚至不知道它的存在
until this research happened.
[AI] 直到这项研究发生。
And they found something really interesting.
[AI] 他们发现了一些非常有趣的东西。
They had to go beyond just helping people
[AI] 他们必须不仅仅是帮助别人
ask their friend to take the photo down.
[AI] 让他们的朋友把照片拍下来。
They had to help people express to their friend
[AI] 他们必须帮助人们向他们的朋友表达自己的想法
how the photo made them feel.
[AI] 照片给他们的感觉。
Here's how the experience works today.
[AI] 这就是今天的体验。
So I find this hypothetical photo of myself.
[AI] 所以我找到了这张我自己的假想照片。
and it's not spam. it's not abuse.
[AI] 这不是垃圾邮件。这不是虐待。
but I really wish it weren't on the site.
[AI] 但我真希望它不在网站上。
So I report it and I say.
[AI] 所以我报告了，我说。
"I'm in this photo and I don't like it."
[AI] “我在这张照片里，我不喜欢它。”
and then we dig deeper.
[AI] 然后我们再深入挖掘。
Why don't you like this photo of yourself?
[AI] 你为什么不喜欢这张你自己的照片？
And I select "It's embarrassing."
[AI] 我选择“这很尴尬”
And then I'm encouraged to message my friend.
[AI] 然后我被鼓励给我的朋友发短信。
but here's the critical difference.
[AI] 但关键的区别在于此。
I'm provided specific suggested language
[AI] 我被提供了具体的建议语言
that helps me communicate to Laura
[AI] 这有助于我与劳拉沟通
how the photo makes me feel.
[AI] 这张照片给我的感觉。
Now the team found that this relatively small change
[AI] 现在研究小组发现这个相对较小的变化
had a huge impact.
[AI] 产生了巨大的影响。
Before. only 20 percent of people
[AI] 之前只有20%的人
were sending the message.
[AI] 我们正在发送消息。
and now 60 percent were.
[AI] 现在有60%的人是。
and surveys showed that people
[AI] 调查显示人们
on both sides of the conversation
[AI] 在谈话的双方
felt better as a result.
[AI] 结果感觉好多了。
That same survey showed
[AI] 同样的调查显示
that 90 percent of your friends
[AI] 你90%的朋友
want to know if they've done something to upset you.
[AI] 想知道他们是否做了什么让你不高兴的事。
Now I don't know who the other 10 percent are.
[AI] 现在我不知道其他10%的人是谁。
but maybe that's where our "Unfriend" feature
[AI] 但也许这就是我们的“不朋友”功能
can come in handy.
[AI] 可以派上用场。
So as you can see.
[AI] 如你所见。
these decisions are highly nuanced.
[AI] 这些决定非常微妙。
Of course we use a lot of data
[AI] 当然，我们使用了大量的数据
to inform our decisions.
[AI] 通知我们的决定。
but we also rely very heavily on iteration.
[AI] 但我们也非常依赖迭代。
research. testing. intuition. human empathy.
[AI] 研究测试。直觉人类的同理心。
It's both art and science.
[AI] 这既是艺术也是科学。
Now. sometimes the designers who work on these products
[AI] 现在有时，设计这些产品的设计师
are called "data-driven."
[AI] 被称为“数据驱动”
which is a term that totally drives us bonkers.
[AI] 这是一个让我们发疯的术语。
The fact is. it would be irresponsible of us
[AI] 事实是。这对我们来说是不负责任的
not to rigorously test our designs
[AI] 不要严格测试我们的设计
when so many people are counting on us
[AI] 当这么多人都指望我们的时候
to get it right.
[AI] 让它正确。
but data analytics
[AI] 但是数据分析
will never be a substitute for design intuition.
[AI] 永远不会取代设计直觉。
Data can help you make a good design great.
[AI] 数据可以帮助你做出一个好的设计。
but it will never made a bad design good.
[AI] 但它永远不会让一个糟糕的设计变好。
The next thing that you need to understand as a principle
[AI] 接下来你需要理解的是一个原则
is that when you introduce change.
[AI] 这就是你引入变革的时候。
you need to do it extraordinarily carefully.
[AI] 你需要格外小心地做这件事。
Now I often have joked that
[AI] 现在我经常开玩笑说
I spend almost as much time
[AI] 我花了几乎同样多的时间
designing the introduction of change
[AI] 设计变革的引入
as I do the change itself.
[AI] 就像我做改变一样。
and I'm sure that we can all relate to that
[AI] 我相信我们都能理解这一点
when something that we use a lot changes
[AI] 当我们经常使用的东西发生变化时
and then we have to adjust.
[AI] 然后我们必须调整。
The fact is. people can become
[AI] 事实是。人可以成为
very efficient at using bad design.
[AI] 非常有效地使用糟糕的设计。
and so even if the change is good for them in the long run.
[AI] 因此，即使这种改变从长远来看对他们有利。
it's still incredibly frustrating when it happens.
[AI] 当它发生时，仍然令人难以置信地沮丧。
and this is particularly true
[AI] 尤其如此
with user-generated content platforms.
[AI] 使用用户生成的内容平台。
because people can rightfully claim a sense of ownership.
[AI] 因为人们可以理所当然地要求拥有感。
It is. after all. their content.
[AI] 它是。毕竟他们的内容。
Now. years ago. when I was working at YouTube.
[AI] 现在几年前。当我在YouTube工作的时候。
we were looking for ways to
[AI] 我们在想办法
encourage more people to rate videos.
[AI] 鼓励更多人对视频进行评分。
and it was interesting because when we looked into the data.
[AI] 这很有趣，因为当我们研究数据时。
we found that almost everyone was exclusively using
[AI] 我们发现几乎每个人都只使用
the highest five-star rating.
[AI] 最高的五星评级。
a handful of people were using
[AI] 少数人正在使用
the lowest one-star.
[AI] 最低的一颗星。
and virtually no one
[AI] 几乎没有人
was using two. three or four stars.
[AI] 他用了两个。三星或四星。
So we decided to simplify
[AI] 所以我们决定简化
into an up-down kind of voting binary model.
[AI] 变成了一个上下两种投票的二元模型。
It's going to be much easier for people to engage with.
[AI] 这将使人们更容易参与。
But people were very attached
[AI] 但是人们都很依恋
to the five-star rating system.
[AI] 到五星评级系统。
Video creators really loved their ratings.
[AI] 视频制作人非常喜欢他们的收视率。
Millions and millions of people
[AI] 千百万人
were accustomed to the old design.
[AI] 我们习惯了旧的设计。
So in order to help people
[AI] 所以为了帮助人们
prepare themselves for change and acclimate to the new design more quickly.
[AI] 为变化做好准备，更快地适应新设计。
we actually published the data graph
[AI] 我们实际上发布了数据图
sharing with the community
[AI] 与社区分享
the rationale for what we were going to do.
[AI] 我们将要做的事情的基本原理。
and it even engaged the larger industry
[AI] 它甚至参与了更大的行业
in a conversation. which resulted in
[AI] 在谈话中。导致
my favorite TechCrunch headline of all time:
[AI] 我最喜欢的TechCrunch头条：
"YouTube Comes to a 5-Star Realization:
[AI] “YouTube实现了五星级：
Its Ratings Are Useless."
[AI] 它的评级毫无用处。"
Now. it's impossible to completely avoid change aversion when you're making changes
[AI] 现在当你做出改变时，不可能完全避免对改变的厌恶
to products that so many people use.
[AI] 许多人使用的产品。
Even though we tried to do all the right things.
[AI] 尽管我们试着做所有正确的事情。
we still received our customary flood
[AI] 我们仍按惯例收到洪水
of video protests and angry emails
[AI] 视频抗议和愤怒的电子邮件
and even a package that had to be scanned by security.
[AI] 甚至是一个需要安全部门扫描的包裹。
but we have to remember
[AI] 但我们必须记住
people care intensely about this stuff.
[AI] 人们非常关心这些东西。
and it's because these products. this work.
[AI] 这是因为这些产品。这项工作。
really. really matters to them.
[AI] 真正地对他们来说真的很重要。
Now. we know that we have to be careful
[AI] 现在我们知道我们必须小心
about paying attention to the details.
[AI] 关于关注细节。
we have to be cognizant about how we use data
[AI] 我们必须认识到我们如何使用数据
in our design process.
[AI] 在我们的设计过程中。
and we have to introduce change
[AI] 我们必须引入变革
very. very carefully.
[AI] 非常非常小心。
Now. these things are all really useful.
[AI] 现在这些东西都很有用。
They're good best practices for designing at scale.
[AI] 它们是大规模设计的最佳实践。
But they don't mean anything
[AI] 但它们没有任何意义
if you don't understand something much more fundamental.
[AI] 如果你不了解更基本的东西。
You have to understand who you are designing for.
[AI] 你必须了解你是为谁设计的。
Now. when you set a goal to design
[AI] 现在当你为设计设定目标时
for the entire human race.
[AI] 为了整个人类。
and you start to engage in that goal in earnest.
[AI] 然后你开始认真地实现这个目标。
at some point you run into the walls
[AI] 在某个时候，你会撞到墙上
of the bubble that you're living in.
[AI] 你生活的泡沫。
Now. in San Francisco. we get a little miffed
[AI] 现在在旧金山。我们有点生气
when we hit a dead cell zone
[AI] 当我们到达死囚区时
because we can't use our phones to navigate
[AI] 因为我们不能用手机导航
to the new hipster coffee shop.
[AI] 去新开的时髦咖啡店。
But what if you had to drive four hours
[AI] 但是如果你不得不开四个小时的车呢
to charge your phone because you had no reliable source of electricity?
[AI] 因为你没有可靠的电源给你的手机充电？
What if you had no access to public libraries?
[AI] 如果你不能进入公共图书馆怎么办？
What if your country had no free press?
[AI] 如果你的国家没有新闻自由怎么办？
What would these products start to mean to you?
[AI] 这些产品对你来说意味着什么？
This is what Google. YouTube and Facebook
[AI] 这就是谷歌所做的。YouTube和Facebook
look like to most of the world.
[AI] 对世界上大多数人来说都是这样。
and it's what they'll look like
[AI] 这就是他们的样子
to most of the next five billion people
[AI] 未来50亿人中的大多数
to come online.
[AI] 来上网。
Designing for low-end cell phones
[AI] 为低端手机设计
is not glamorous design work.
[AI] 这不是迷人的设计作品。
but if you want to design for the whole world.
[AI] 但是如果你想为全世界设计。
you have to design for where people are.
[AI] 你必须为人们所在的地方设计。
and not where you are.
[AI] 而不是你现在的位置。
So how do we keep this big. big picture in mind?
[AI] 那么，我们如何保持这样的规模呢。大局在心中？
We try to travel outside of our bubble to see. hear
[AI] 我们试图走出我们的泡沫去看。听见
and understand the people we're designing for.
[AI] 了解我们为之设计的人。
We use our products in non-English languages
[AI] 我们使用非英语语言的产品
to make sure that they work just as well.
[AI] 确保它们也能正常工作。
And we try to use one of these phones from time to time
[AI] 我们会不时尝试使用这些手机中的一款
to keep in touch with their reality.
[AI] 与他们的现实保持联系。
So what does it mean to design at a global scale?
[AI] 那么，在全球范围内进行设计意味着什么呢？
It means difficult and sometimes exasperating work
[AI] 这意味着困难的，有时是令人恼火的工作
to try to improve and evolve products.
[AI] 努力改进和改进产品。
Finding the audacity and the humility to do right by them
[AI] 找到勇气和谦逊，让他们做正确的事
can be pretty exhausting.
[AI] 可能会很累。
and the humility part.
[AI] 还有谦逊的部分。
it's a little tough on the design ego.
[AI] 这对设计自我来说有点难。
Because these products are always changing.
[AI] 因为这些产品总是在变化。
everything that I've designed in my career
[AI] 我在职业生涯中设计的一切
is pretty much gone.
[AI] 已经差不多消失了。
and everything that I will design will fade away.
[AI] 我要设计的一切都会消失。
But here's what remains:
[AI] 但剩下的是：
the never-ending thrill
[AI] 永无止境的激动
of being a part of something that is so big.
[AI] 成为如此巨大事物的一部分。
you can hardly get your head around it.
[AI] 你几乎无法控制它。
and the promise that it just might change the world.
[AI] 以及它可能改变世界的承诺。
Thank you.
[AI] 非常感谢。
(Applause)
[AI] （掌声）